{
    "name": "Sample Deck",
    "cards": [
        {
            "tags" : ["vocabulary"],
            "topics": [],
            "front": "Synonym of 'happy'",
            "back": "Joyful"
        },
        {
            "tags" : [],
            "topics": [],
            "front": "Past tense of 'go'",
            "back": "Went"
        },
        {
            "tags" : [],
            "topics": [],
            "front": "Plural of 'child'",
            "back": "Children"
        },
        {
            "tags" : ["vocabulary"],
            "topics": [],
            "front": "What's the opposite of 'early'?",
            "back": "Late"
        },
        {
            "tags" : [],
            "topics": [],
            "front": "Translate to English: 'pies'",
            "back": "Dog"
        },
        {
            "tags" : [],
            "topics": [],
            "front": "Article before 'apple'",
            "back": "An"
        },
        {
            "tags" : [],
            "topics": [],
            "front": "What's the comparative of 'fast'?",
            "back": "Faster"
        },
        {
            "tags" : [],
            "topics": [],
            "front": "What do you call a female 'actor'?",
            "back": "Actress"
        },
        {
            "tags" : [],
            "topics": [],
            "front": "How do you say 'dziękuję' in English?",
            "back": "Thank you"
        },
        {
            "tags" : [],
            "topics": [],
            "front": "Verb in 'She is reading a book.'",
            "back": "Reading"
        },
        {
            "tags" : [],
            "topics": [],
            "front": "Opposite of 'expensive'",
            "back": "Cheap"
        },
        {
            "tags" : [],
            "topics": [],
            "front": "Which tense? 'He has eaten.'",
            "back": "Present perfect"
        }
    ]
}